{
    "subject": "resource/Athletics_at_the_1952_Summer_Olympics_\u2013_Men's_4_\u00d7_100_metres_relay",
    "predicate": "ontology/silverMedalist",
    "object": "resource/Vladimir_Sukharev",
    "human_readable": "Vladimir Sukharev was a silver medalist in the men's 4x100 metres relay at the 1952 Summer Olympics.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.939145028591156,
            "question": "In what year did Vladimir Sukharev win a silver medal at the Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9359853863716125,
            "question": "What event did Vladimir Sukharev win a silver medal in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9282360076904297,
            "question": "What sport did Vladimir Sukharev compete in at the 1952 Summer Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8100053071975708,
            "question": "Was Vladimir Sukharev part of a team that won a medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7957313656806946,
            "question": "Which Olympics did Vladimir Sukharev participate in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.779436469078064,
            "question": "Who competed with Vladimir Sukharev on the relay team?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.770379900932312,
            "question": "What color medal did Vladimir Sukharev win?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7655670046806335,
            "question": "What type of Olympics did Vladimir Sukharev compete in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.639367401599884,
            "question": "Did Vladimir Sukharev compete in an individual or team event?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6272121667861938,
            "question": "Was Vladimir Sukharev's medal awarded for a track or field event?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Vladimir Sukharev was a silver medalist in the men's 4x100 metres relay at the 1952 Summer Olympics.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6336_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Vladimir Sukharev compete in an individual or team event?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6336_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of Olympics did Vladimir Sukharev compete in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6336_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What color medal did Vladimir Sukharev win?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6336_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6336_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6336_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6336_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6336_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6336_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6336_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6336_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6336_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6336_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6336_51.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe information provided in the documents supports that Vladimir Sukharev was indeed a silver medalist in the men's 4x100 metres relay at the 1952 Summer Olympics, which aligns with the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}